Sorry, Jami Website is not available in your language at the moment, but we are working on it! We offer the English language, by default.

*   Donate

Privacy Policy
==============

Jami is a peer to peer universal and distributed communication software that upholds its users freedom and privacy. At Jami, we think that privacy is a fundamental right on the Internet. Everybody should be free not to give personal data to corporations in order to benefit from an essential service on the Internet. We know better than anyone else why personal information is sensitive, what our responsibility is to protect it, and what our duties are.

Jami Website

Why we process your information

On Jami website, we only collect anonymous and aggregated data for the analysis of the website activity. We obtain session information (browser, time spent, page visits, referring sites, etc.)  
  
Statistics are used to better know our users and therefore focus our energies and development on most popular platforms. It also encourage translations into languages that could be neglected.

How we use “cookies”

We use reporting and analytic cookies from Matomo to collect information about how you use our website. These cookies only gather information for statistical purposes and do not allow to directly identify you. You can refer to [Matomo Privacy Policy](https://matomo.org/privacy-policy/) for more details.

Jami Application

Why Jami is secure

Jami protects your privacy and your communications. Jami relies on a fully distributed network and offers direct peer-to-peer communications between users. It gives the insurance that all your communications do no transit through any servers.  
  
Jami offers a secure and private communication environment. All connections are end-to-end encrypted. We use state of the art end-to-end encryption with perfect forward secrecy for all communications and comply with the X.509 standard. We use TLS/SRTP to secure connection and communications over the network.

Jami account and personal information

Jami does not require any personal information to create an account and to communicate. No email, no phone number are required. Your account is only stored on your device and contains a pair of public and private keys used to encrypt all your communications. A unique Jami ID is associated to your account and can be shared and used to communicate with other Jami users. We offer an optional username management system that allows you to associate a username to your Jami ID. Usernames are stored in a public Ethereum blockchain-based registry, thus preserving the distributed aspect of Jami. Once created, a username cannot be transferred, deleted or modified.  
  
Savoir-faire Linux also offers a free public DHT proxy service to provide a better support of push notifications on mobiles. A TURN server is also available to ease the connectivity for users who are in a private network, in case a peer-to-peer connection can not be established. Both services do not store any logs or personal information and can be deactivated from the application settings if wanted.

How to delete a Jami account

There are three ways to delete your Jami account, either directly in the application or software, by deleting the data from the software, or by deleting the app on your mobile device:

1. You can manually delete your account directly in Jami, by going to the account settings and clicking on "Delete account"; you must do this on all devices on which you have set up your Jami account for the account deletion to be effective.
2. You can also delete the Jami application or software data, which will also delete the Jami account on that device.
3. On mobile devices (iOS and Android), deleting the Jami application and its data will delete the account on that device.

Software use

Last but not least, Jami is a free/libre software. You can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version. The source code can be found [here](https://git.jami.net/savoirfairelinux).

Jami needs your support!

Our mission is to provide all human beings with a free, secure communications software that respects their privacy and values.

Your donation will help us carry on with this mission by enabling this project to progress, thrive, and reach more people every day.

Could you lend us a hand?

[Donation FAQ](https://jami.net/whydonate/#donation-faq) · [Contact us](mailto:contact@jami.net) · [Privacy Policy](https://jami.net/privacy-policy)

Donate to Jami

Once

Monthly

  Donate

Make a donation of to Jami

  Credit card

To make a recurring donation, use Paypal as a payment method.  

Other method to [donate](https://jami.net/whydonate/#payment-check)

Credit card

Full name 

Email 

Credit card

Donate now

Thank you for supporting Jami!

Your donation means a lot! With your help, we can continue to provide a free, secure, and private communication software for all.  
  
Your generosity fuels our mission to keep communication private and accessible.

Subscribe to our newsletter **to be the first to know** about the latest Jami updates!

 I have read and agree to the Privacy policy

😭

Donation failed

We're sorry, it appears that your payment couldn't be processed.  
  
Please contact your bank or try [another payment method](https://jami.net/whydonate/#payment-check).  
  
Your contribution means a lot to us, thank you for your support and understanding.

Try again

Can I cancel my recurring donation?

You can visit our donation FAQ page to find the appropriate response according to your payment method or reach out to us at [contact@jami.net](mailto:contact@jami.net)

Free and private sharing. Donate to expand it.

 Donate

Subscribe to our newsletter

 I have read and agree to the Privacy policy

Jami is available on all platforms

  Donate

* Jami

* Professionals

* Help

* Donate
